Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art buildings and grounds records, 1870-2007 COR0007.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Architectural drawings, 1870-1981; Series 6; 325 item(s)
  - [Exhibition galleries: 24, 25, 26, 28, 29, 30], 1980s; Series 6; 6 sheet(s); 26 x 19 (Box RG7.0-2008.017, Item 4)
  - Basic structure: sub-basement, basement, 1st, 2nd & 3rd, roof, 1984; Series 6; 4 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.017, Item 5)
  - Air conditioning of 1st and 2nd floor galleries (1st floor), 1981; Series 6; 1 sheet(s); 45 x 36 (Box RG7.0-2008.017, Item 6)
    Adams
  - Floor plans: basement, 1st, 2nd & 3rd, 1984; Series 6; 28 x 23 (Box RG7.0-2008.017, Item 7)
  - Proposed new building, 1980; Series 6; 36 x 25 (Box RG7.0-2008.017, Item 8)
    Koubek
  - Hammer auditorium, 1980; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.017, Item 9)
  - Hammer auditorium, 1980; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.017, Item 10)
  - Floor plans, First and Second Floor (two copies ), undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.018, Item 1)
  - Schedules and controls, 1981; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.018, Item 2)
  - Copies of Corcoran floor plans, 1926; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.018, Item 3)
  - Hispanic Art in America Rough Layout, 1987; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.018, Item 4)
    Castro
  - Basic structure: sub-basement, basement, 1st floor, roof, 1984; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.018, Item 5)
  - Roof plan, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.018, Item 6)
    Greenhorne
  - Basic Structure Basement and Sub-Basement, 1984; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.018, Item 7)
  - Basement and Sub-Basement, Undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.018, Item 8)
  - Plot plan, 1966; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.018, Item 9)
    FSFF
  - Air conditioning of 1st and 2nd floor as built, 1983; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.018, Item 10)
  - Hammer Auditorium Revised Dimming Diagram, 1980; Series 6; 3 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.018, Item 11)
  - School Layout, 1989; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 1)
  - Basic Structure First, Second, Third floor and Roof, 1984; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 2)
  - Basic Structure Sub Basement, Basement, First Floor, Roof and Third Floor, 1984; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 3)
  - The Lansburgh's Site Proposal, 1986; Series 6; 20 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 4)
  - Space Program for Studios, 1986; Series 6; 18 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 5)
    Lansart
  - School Floor Plan, Undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 6)
  - Print Making Laboratory, 1985; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 7)
  - Twelve Hundred Fifteenth Street Hearing Submission, 1988; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 8)
  - School Layout and First Floor Plan, Undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 9)
  - Existing Building Sub-Basement, Basement, First Floor, Second and Third Floor, 1987; Series 6; 16 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 10)
  - Photography School (Photocopy), 1990; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 11)
  - Twelve Hundred Fifteenth Street Revision and Copies, 1989; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 12)
  - Basic structure: sub-basement, basement, 1st, roof, 1984; Series 6; 4 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 13)
  - Ground Floor Plan, Undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 14)
  - Basic Structure First Floor, Roof and Third Floor, basement and Sub-Basement, 1984; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 15)
  - Color Photography Studios, 1990; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 16)
  - Rough Sketches, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 17)
  - Space Program for Studios Small Version, 1986; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 18)
  - 15th and M Street Plans, Undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 19)
  - Room Details, 1986; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.019, Item 20)
  - Accessibility for the handicapped, 1982; Series 6; 4 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.020, Item 1)
    WFJB
  - Accessibility for the handicapped, 1983; Series 6; 10 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.020, Item 2)
  - Cross-section, sub-basement, baseument, 1st, 2nd, 1968; Series 6; 9 sheet(s) mylar (Box RG7.0-2008.020, Item 3)
  - 2nd floor HVAC/Electrical, attic & room; HVAC/Electrical, 1981; Series 6; 2 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.020, Item 4)
  - 1st floor & lobby remodeling, floor plan and elevations; casework details, 1960; Series 6; 2 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.020, Item 5)
  - Gallery 3 renovation (development office), 1986; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.020, Item 6)
  - Air conditioning of 1st and 2nd floor galleries, 1981; Series 6; 7 sheet(s) mylar (Box RG7.0-2008.020, Item 7)
  - Floor plans: roof, 1984; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.020, Item 8)
    Spreiregen?
  - Accessibility to handicapped, 1982; Series 6; 4 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.020, Item 9)
  - Temperature controls, 1982; Series 6; 6 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.020, Item 10)
    Johnson Controls
  - CGA office building, 1987; Series 6; 34 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.020, Item 11)
    Hartman Cox
  - CGA office building (2 bid sets), 1987-1989; Series 6; 78 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 1)
  - CGA office building: security alarm system, 1989; Series 6; 14 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 2)
    Ralph Ward
  - CGA office building, undated; Series 6; 3 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 3)
  - [CGA office building: NY Ave elevation], 1987; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 4)
    Willard/Hartman Cox
  - CGA office building: preliminary construction schedule, undated; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 5)
    Hyman Construction
  - Asbestos investigation drawings, 1980; Series 6; 5 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 6)
    ATEC
  - [CGA office building: interior lobby design], undated; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 7)
  - CGA office building, 1986; Series 6; 23 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 8)
  - CGA office building, 1986; Series 6; 17 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 9)
  - CGA office building, 1987; Series 6; 18 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 10)
  - [Proposed office building], undated; Series 6; 11 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 11)
  - CGA office building: offices for Baker & McKenzie, 1986; Series 6; 3 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 12)
  - Basic structure: sub-basement, basement, 1st, 2nd & 3rd, roof, 1984; Series 6; 5 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 13)
  - [Proposed office building], undated; Series 6; 3 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 14)
  - CGA office building: NY Ave elevations, 1987; Series 6; 3 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 15)
  - CGA office building: preliminary construction schedule, undated; Series 6; 2 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 16)
  - [CGA office building: NY Ave elevation], 1987; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.021, Item 17)
  - Floor plans: sub-basement, basement, 1st, 2nd & 3rd, 1984; Series 6; 4 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.022, Item 1)
  - Floor plans: sub-basement, basement, 1st, 2nd & 3rd, 1984; Series 6; 4 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.022, Item 2)
  - Floor plans: basement, 1984; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.022, Item 3)
  - CGA office building (not for construction), 1987; Series 6; 105 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.022, Item 4)
  - CGA office building [floor plans], undated; Series 6; 72 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.022, Item 5)
    Depui
  - Corcoran Gallery [floor plans], 1978; Series 6; 7 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.022, Item 6)
    Hugh Newell Jacobson
  - Modern copies of 1895 NJSI drawings, undated; Series 6; 20 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.022, Item 7)
  - Modern copy of 1926 Platt drawing, undated; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.022, Item 8)
  - Floor plans: sub-basement, basement, 1st, 2nd & 3rd, 1984; Series 6; 4 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.022, Item 9)
  - CGA office building, 1988; Series 6; 63 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.022, Item 10)
  - CGA Photography School, 1990; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.023, Item 1)
  - 1680 Wisconsin Avenue: CSA, 1989; Series 6; 3 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.023, Item 2)
  - [CGA office building: NY Ave elevation], 1987; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.023, Item 3)
  - [CGA office building: NY Ave elevation], undated; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.023, Item 4)
  - Modern copies of Platt drawings and roof plans, 1964; Series 6; 35 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.023, Item 5)
    Greenhouse & O'Mara
  - Modern copies of Platt drawings and Faulkner, Fryer & Vanderpool floor plans, undated; Series 6; 15 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.023, Item 6)
  - CGA office building, 1986; Series 6; 10 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.023, Item 7)
  - [proposed office building], undated; Series 6; 14 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.023, Item 8)
  - CGA office building, 1987; Series 6; 13 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.023, Item 9)
  - Sub-basement, basement, 1st floor, 2nd floor, cross section, 1971; Series 6; 15 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 1)
  - Sub-basement, undated; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 2)
  - Design for vestibule information center, 1977; Series 6; 1 sheet(s); graph paper (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 3)
  - Plan view of roof on Flagg wing of CGA, undated; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 4)
  - Hammer Auditorium, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 5)
  - Sub-basement, 1972; Series 6; 9 copies; 9 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 6)
  - Basement, 1st floor, 2nd floor, 1968; Series 6; 3 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 7)
  - Cross section, 1971; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 8)
  - Details of stage doors, Corcoran auditorium, 1980; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 9)
  - Elevator hoistway doors, 1980; Series 6; 9 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 10)
  - [roof duct work?], 1982?; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 11)
  - Hammer auditorium: details, 1980; Series 6; 5 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 12)
  - Hammer auditorium: electrical, 1980; Series 6; 4 copies; 4 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 13)
  - Hammer auditorium: hoistway doors, 1980; Series 6; 2 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 14)
  - Guard's station: rough plan: east basement, undated; Series 6; 2 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 15)
  - Proposed spaces for re-installation of American collection, 2nd floor, undated; Series 6; 2 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 16)
  - [Hammer auditorium: interior drawing], undated; Series 6; 1 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 17)
  - Director's room and secs., 1972; Series 6; 2 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 18)
  - Basement; 1st floor; 2nd floor, 1972; Series 6; 13 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 19)
  - Floor plans, 1st floor; 2nd floor, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.024, Item 20)
  - Outline Specifications for Parking Facilities, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 1)
  - Detail of Stage Door, Corcoran Auditorium, 1980 July 23; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 2)
  - Sub-Basement and Basement Plan, 1978 July 21; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 3)
  - Second Floor HVAC & Electrical, Attic Demolition, Attic and Roof HVAC and Electrical Plan, Attic Ventilation and Shading, 1981 August 14; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 4)
  - Auditorium First Floor Plan, Sections, 1979 October 31; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 5)
  - Hammer Auditorium Plans and Section, 1980 June 16; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 6)
  - Hammer Auditorium Basement Demolition Plans, First Floor & Part. Roof, First floor Demolition, First Floor Electrical, 1980; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 7)
  - Air Conditioning of First and Second Floor Galleries, 1981 August 14; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 8)
  - Heating and Ventilation Basement Studio, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 9)
  - Hammer Auditorium First Floor Plan, Sections, Lobby Elevations, 1980 March; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 10)
  - Hammer Auditorium Sections and First Floor Plan - Electrical, 1980 March; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 11)
  - Basement, First, and Second Floor Plan, 1968 October 24; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 12)
  - Basement, Second Floor, and Sub-Basement Floor Plan, 1971 January 4; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 13)
  - [Fire Damage to plan], undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 14)
  - Headquarters Building for United Unions, INC, 1970; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 15)
  - Photocopy Sub-Basement, Basement, First Floor, Second Floor, Cross Section Plan, 1971 January 4; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 16)
  - Electrical Renovations Basement, First Floor, Second Floor, Power Risers, 1964 June 8; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 17)
  - Auditorium Basement Demolition, Basement and Floor Plan, First Floor Demolition, First Floor Plan Electrical, 1980 May 9; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 18)
  - Photocopy Cross Section Thru Building, Sub-Basement, Basement, First, Second Floor Plan, 1971 January 4; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 19)
  - Alterations to Provide Accessibility For the Handicapped, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 20)
  - CAC Prelims, 1981 January; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.025, Item 21)
  - New World Shop Plans, 1983 September 14; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 1)
  - New World Shop Plans (Second Copy), 1983 September 14; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 2)
  - Air Conditioning of First and Second Floor Galeries, 1981 September 14; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 3)
  - Gallery S17 Air Conditioning, 1977 March 18; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 4)
  - Photocopy - Second Floor Plan, Cross Section Thru Building, basement Floor Plan, First floor plan, 1971 January 4; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 5)
  - Roof Plan Transparency, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 6)
  - Auditorium Plans, 1980 March; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 7)
  - Sketches for Reinstillation of American Collections, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 8)
  - photocopy - sub-basement, basement, first floor, second floor, cross section, 1971 January 4; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 9)
  - Floor Plans, 1971 - 1984; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 10)
  - Gallery Floor Plans, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 11)
  - Air Conditioning Schematic - Print Making Laboratory, 1983 January 10; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 12)
  - Gallery 16 Geo. Wash Partition, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 13)
  - Torn half of First 8 Second Floor Core Plans, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.026, Item 14)
  - Copy of Copper Gutter Detials, 1926 November 24; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.027, Item 1)
  - Wisconsin Court Renovations Site Plans, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.027, Item 2)
  - Wisconsin Court Renovations Details and Floor Plans, 1988; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.027, Item 3)
  - Rehabilitation of the Fillmore School Design Development Package, 1998; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.027, Item 4)
  - Corcoran Gallery Boundary and Topography Survey, 2001 October; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.027, Item 5)
  - Rehabilitation of the Fillmore School Design Development Package, 1998 April 22; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.027, Item 6)
  - Rehabilitation of the Fillmore School Design Development Package, 1998 June 25; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.027, Item 7)
  - Sub-Basement HVAC and Electrical, 1981 August 14; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.028, Item 1)
  - Basement Plan Existing Building, 1988 June 8; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.028, Item 2)
  - CGA Office Building, 1989 February 3; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.028, Item 3)
  - Drawing of Bicentenial Proposal #2, 1975 August 14; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.029, Item 1)
  - Song of My People Exhibition Plans, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.029, Item 2)
  - Demolition and New Construction Plans, 1989 June 27; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.029, Item 3)
  - Photocopy Plans: First Floor, Basement, Sub-Basement, Second and Third Floor, 1984 March; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.029, Item 4)
  - Sub Basement, 1984 March; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.029, Item 5)
  - Plans Gallery 19-26, 28-30, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.029, Item 6)
  - Non-Bearing Partision and Door Details, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.029, Item 7)
  - Foundation and Framing Plans, 1988 June 8; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.029, Item 8)
  - Rehabilitation of the Fillmore School Development Package, 1998 April 22; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.029, Item 9)
  - Demolition and New Construction Plans: Basement, First Floor, Second Floor, 1989 June 27; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.029, Item 10)
  - A Brush With Disney - The Art of Herbert Dickens Ryman Exhbition Sketches, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.030, Item 1)
  - Posters and Map from African-American Artist Exhibitons, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.030, Item 2)
  - Copy of Blueprints: Elevations for Additions tot he Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1926 May 15; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.030, Item 3)
  - Air Condition of First and Second Gallery plans, 1981 August 14; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.030, Item 4)
  - Demolition and New Construction: Basement, First Floor, Second Floor, 1989 June 27; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.030, Item 5)
  - Basement, First, Second, Third Floor Plans, 1989 March 16; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.030, Item 6)
  - Rough Gallery and Floor Plans, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.030, Item 7)
  - Copy, Second and Third Floor Plan, 1984 March; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.030, Item 8)
  - Highlighted Copy, First Floor Plan, 1984 March; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.030, Item 9)
  - Basement Floor Plan, 1984 March; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.030, Item 10)
  - Photocopy, Gallery Plans, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.030, Item 11)
  - HVAC and Electrical Second Floor and Attic and Roof, 1981 August 14; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 1)
  - Electrical Renovations, 1964 July 1; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 2)
  - Electrical Renovations and Electrical Plans, 1964 July 1; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 3)
  - Cealing BluePrints, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 4)
  - As-Built HVAC and Electrical, 1982 February 22; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 5)
  - Electrical Renovations - Basement, Second Floor, First Floor, 1964 July 1; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 6)
  - Electrical Renovations - Received Stamp, 1964 July 1; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 7)
  - Anotated Copy of Floor Plans - Roof, Basement, Heating and Ventilation, 1976 June 1; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 8)
  - Copy of Basement Floor Plan, Sub Basement, First, Second Floor, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 9)
  - Air Conditioning Concepts, 1979 February; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 10)
  - Existing Electrical Panels, 1964 May 22; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 11)
  - Gallery S17 Air Conditioning, 1977 March 18; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 12)
  - Unlabeled Blue Prints, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 13)
  - Basic Structure Blue Prints, 1984 March; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 14)
  - Cross Section Thru Building, Sub-Basement, Basement, Second Floor Plan, 1971 January 4; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 15)
  - Air Conditioning Concepts, 1979; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 16)
  - Clark Wing Pipe and Angle Supports, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.031, Item 17)
  - Basement Floor Plan Demolition and New Construction, 1989 June 27; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.007, Item 1)
  - Floor Plans 100 percent Progress Print, 2000 August 1; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.007, Item 2)
  - Corcoran Blue Prints, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.007, Item 3)
  - Corcoran Floor Plans, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.007, Item 4)
  - Atrium Floor plan, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.007, Item 5)
  - Boundary and Topography Survey, 2001 October; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.007, Item 6)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building, 1987 June 12; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.007, Item 7)
  - First Floor Level Plan, 2000 May 26; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.007, Item 8)
  - First Floor, Second and Third Floor, Basement, 1984 March; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.007, Item 9)
  - Basic Structure Basement, First Floor, Second Floor, Roof, Sub-basement, 1984 March; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.007, Item 10)
  - Warehouse Plan Demolition, 2001 August 10; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.007, Item 11)
  - Security Alarm System Single Line Riser Diagram, 1990 February 15; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.007, Item 12)
  - Restroom sign, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.007, Item 13)
  - Gehry Expansion Plans, 2003 August 1; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.008, Item 1)
  - Gehry Expansion Plans - Plumbing, 2003 August 1; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.008, Item 2)
  - Gehry Partnerships renovations floorplans, 2001 November 16; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.009, Item 1)
  - Gehry - Partial Floor Plan, 2001 October 26; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.009, Item 2)
  - Gehry - Landscape Plan, 2003 May 2; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.009, Item 3)
  - Gehry - Additions building notes and key of symbols, Cabling Plans, 2003 August 1; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.010, Item 1)
  - Gehry - General Notes Sheet 2, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.010, Item 2)
  - Gehry - Existing Conditions Plan, 2002 October 4; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.011, Item 1)
  - Gehry - Existing Conditions Plan - Grounds, 2002 May 31; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.011, Item 2)
  - Gehry - Corcoran Floor Plans, 2001 September 10; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.011, Item 3)
  - Gehry - Corcoran Construction Plans, 2003 May 2; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.011, Item 4)
  - Gehry - Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building - Transparencies, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.011, Item 5)
  - Hartman Cox - Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building (unbuilt), 1989 March 10; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.013, Item 1)
  - Hartman Cox - Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building (unbuilt), 1988 June 8; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.013, Item 2)
  - Hartman Cox - Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building (unbuilt), 1989 March 10; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.013, Item 3)
  - Gehry - Food Service Plans, 2003 March 28; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.014, Item 1)
  - Gehry - Lighting Plans, 2002 October 25; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.014, Item 2)
  - Technical Documents - Phase 1 (Gehry Partners, LLP), 2002 May 31; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.014, Item 3)
  - Gehry and Associates Foundation Plan, Basement Framing Plan, First Floor, Second Floor, Skylight, Roof, Foundation Wall, 2000 August 26; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.014, Item 4)
  - Gehry - Landscape Plan, 2003 February 7; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.014, Item 5)
  - Gehry - Steam and Heating Plans, 1965 April; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.014, Item 6)
  - Gehry - Floor Plan 95 percent Progress Print, 2000 May 26; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.014, Item 7)
  - Gehry - Corcoran Gallery Sub-Basement Plans, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.014, Item 8)
  - Gehry - Building Grid Survey and Spot Elevation and Parapet Elevation Survey, 2002 July 26; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.014, Item 9)
  - United States Institute of Peace Blueprints, 2002 May; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.015, Item 1)
  - Gallery Floor Plans, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.015, Item 2)
  - 1st and 2nd Floor Plans "additions to Corcoran Gallery", 1925 September 21; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.015, Item 3)
  - Fillmore School Playground, 2000 July 11; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.015, Item 4)
  - Corcoran Parking Levels, 1989 November 21; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.015, Item 5)
  - Topographic Map (3 copies), 2000 July 14; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.015, Item 6)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building Core Plans, 1989 March 10; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.015, Item 7)
  - Details and Elevations from Gehry Partners, LLP, 2002 November 4; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.015, Item 8)
  - FOG & Associates - Plans, 2001 May 25; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.015, Item 9)
  - Alterations and Additions Copies, 1960 May 12; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.015, Item 10)
  - Plat of Survey, 2001 September 13; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.015, Item 11)
  - Randall Jr. High School Addition, 1967; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.015, Item 12)
  - Fillmore School Playground, 2000 May 19; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.016, Item 1)
  - Topographic Map Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1986 March 3; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.016, Item 2)